Hardiksingh Hada

International Marketer (MBA) [IND/AUS/USA]

B-405, Surel Apartments, Bodakdev, Ahmedabad - 380054 +91-7600089521 Hardik.hada@gmail.com

SKILLS

Experienced International Marketing Executive with a demonstrated history of communication, leadership and problem solving abilities not just in the building materials, but also in the corporate culture, handling the accounts of clients to building an entire new list of accounts in the continent be it marketing, advertising, accounts, logistics and closing the deals.

EXPERIENCE

Italia Group (Piccolo Mosaics Ltd.), Ahmedabad - Assistant Manager

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

- Biggest Account handling for the company in the Oceania Market.
- Creating new accounts across the Asia Pacific.

Italia Group (Piccolo Mosaics Ltd.), Ahmedabad - Intl Mktg Executive

March 2019 - MARCH 2021

- Handling day to day activities for the key accounts.
- Traveling to meet clients Australia, Fiji, NZ and SEA Countries.
- Developing Virgin territory (Oceania) for the company and scale it to INR 5 Cr. and growing.

EDUCATION

KSV, Gandhinagar (INDIA) - MBA (Pharmacy)

AUGUST 2012 - OCTOBER 2014

Swinburne University, Melbourne (AUS) - M.Com. (Intl Business)

FEBRUARY 2015 - OCTOBER 2016

Northeastern University, Boston (USA) - MS (PJM)

JANUARY 2017 - OCTOBER 2018